This way of working was so successful
这种工作方式非常成功，
that Ford immediately began trying to
福特立即开始尝试将
use it for more complex parts. Normally,
其应用于更复杂的零部件。 通常情况下，
cars would be assembled on a stand by a
汽车会由一群技术娴熟的工匠在支架上组装
team of skilled craftsmen. Almost
。 几乎
nothing was automated and a lot of time
没有任何自动化操作，工人花费大量时间在
factory and bringing parts to the car.
工厂里走来走去，把零件送到汽车旁。
Any delay in a single task meant that
任何一个环节的延误都意味着
the other workers had to wait to do
其他工人必须等待才能完成
their task. The whole process was slow
他们的任务。 整个过程既缓慢
and expensive. And a typical car company
又昂贵。 像凯迪拉克这样的普通汽车公司
around 2,000 cars each year. To make
每年只能生产大约 2000 辆汽车。 要想让
cars affordable for the masses, they'd
汽车成为大众都能负担得起的商品，就
have to be produced in enormous
必须大规模生产汽车
quantities. And no one understood this
。 而没有人
more than the Ford Motor Company.
比福特汽车公司更明白这一点。   人们
Henry Ford himself often gets credit for
常常将亨利·福特将
turning his factory into an assembly
工厂改造成
line. But in reality, the idea came from
流水线的功劳归于他本人。 但实际上，这个想法来自
one of Ford's production engineers,
福特公司的一位生产工程师
William Klann.
威廉·克兰。
At the start of 1913, he visited a meat
1913年初，他参观了芝加哥的一家肉类
packing factory in Chicago, which was
加工厂，这家工厂
known to be one of the most efficient
被誉为当时全国效率最高的
factories in the country. When he was
工厂之一。 当他
there, he was amazed by what he saw.
身临其境时，他被眼前所见的一切深深震撼了。
The animals were hung from a rail on a
这些动物被悬挂在
ceiling and moved to various stations
天花板的轨道上，然后被运送到工厂周围的各个工位，
around the factory where they were cut
在那里它们被
up, processed, [music] and packaged,
切割、加工、包装，
ready to be shipped out. The whole
准备装运出去。 整个
process was simplified down to the most
流程被简化为
basic tasks and spread across multiple
最基本的任务，并分配给多名
workers.
工作人员完成。
This gave William an idea. Although this
这给了威廉一个主意。 虽然这种
process worked for taking apart an
方法适用于分解
animal, [music]
动物，但（音乐）
perhaps it could work for putting
或许也适用于
together a car.
组装汽车。
He took the idea to Ford and they
他把这个想法告诉了福特公司，福特公司
immediately began testing it out on a
立即开始在一个
relatively simple part, the flywheel
相对简单的部件——飞轮
magneto.
磁电机上进行测试。
Normally, a team of 30 workers would
通常情况下，一个由 30 名工人组成的团队会
each assemble entire magnetos at
在
individual workbenches. With this setup,
各自的工作台上组装整个磁电机。 按照这种配置，
[music] day.
每天可以生产大约 800 个磁体。
Ford got rid of the workbenches and
福特公司拆除了工作台，
installed a single long steel table. The
安装了一张长长的钢制工作台。
workers were arranged in specific
工人们被安排在特定的
[music] positions and instead of
（音乐）位置上，
assembling a complete magneto, they were
他们不是组装一个完整的磁电机，而是被
told to only perform a single task and
告知只执行一项任务，然后将
slide the magneto onto the next person.
磁电机滑到下一个人身上。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Since each worker was just repeating the
由于每个工人只是重复
same task, it brought the total assembly
同样的任务，因此总组装
time down from 20 minutes to just 13
时间从 20 分钟减少到 13
minutes.
分钟。
To speed up the process even more, Ford
为了进一步加快生产速度，福特用一条
that moved at a constant speed. This
以恒定速度运行的传送带取代了工作台。 这
caused the slow workers to speed up and
导致速度慢的工人加快速度，速度
the fastest workers to slow down,
快的工人放慢速度，从而
balancing out the line and keeping
平衡了生产线，使
everything in [music] sync.
一切保持[音乐]同步。
In just a few months, Ford went from
短短几个月内，福特的
producing 800 magnetos a day to almost
磁电机日产量就从 800 个增加到近
3,000.
3000 个。